{
    "id": "f50c2539ebe34d4fbb0fd1f444c56bd6",
    "title": "At, In And On",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He gets …………………. the market by bike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24af48f54be94184a14cb7bb6814b660"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents live ………………….Singapore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89f1be6e666d4c58b2d22f3983c96d5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I go ……………………. Singapore to see them whenever I can.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3ca36a8803604017b826ef60ff848d7b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to see my parents ……………………. Singapore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d341c318f944683976abc51f9289034"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go …………………….. Marcel’s for coffee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "486dd9fd904d4712a64cf0f6cfdadc72"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go and have tea ……………………. Smith’s.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2f915061e054426b82682b5065ebda1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ……………………. me like this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "409bf3de71d547d29e91e1bb8973fafa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stop throwing stones …………………… the cats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3462be205aa74b90964270dea7876f02"
        },
        {
            "question": "When did you arrive …………………….. Mexico?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f91a3a038f0c49aeac96f06d7f56113a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you shout …………………. James and tell him it is time he started.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef2d77f3fddc44cb8933e3b878761892"
        }
    ]
}